eztrader.com 2015-06-08

# Binary Options | EZTrader.com | Privacy Statement

##  Your privacy, our priority

Protecting the privacy and safeguarding the personal and financial information of our clients and website visitors is one of our highest priorities. The following Privacy Statement explains how EZTrader collects and protects your personal information.

By opening an EZTrader account or by using this Web site, you give your consent to the collection and use of personal information by EZTrader as explained in this Privacy Statement.

##  Collection of personal information

We collect information required to open an account, to transact business effectively and to safeguard your privacy. To do this, we gather information to help us assess your needs and preferences.

The information we collect directly from you includes information required to communicate with you, including your name, mailing address, telephone number and e-mail address. In addition, we collect information required by law to identify who you are, including your Passport number or Tax Identification number. We also collect demographic information when you open an account, including gender and birth date.

You directly provide to us the majority of information we collect. You do this by completing the account application and related documentation, by placing a trade, by sending us an e-mail, or by submitting information in response to a promotion or special offer. Other ways we obtain information are by (1) observing your usage of our Web site, and (2) providing products and services to you. This information enables us to offer you products and services that should be of interest to you.

The information we collect indirectly from you includes your Internet protocol ("IP") address, browser type, operating system, Internet service provider (ISP), time stamps, transactions placed, and banner ads you click. We do this through the use of cookies, which are small text files sent from the Web server and may be stored on your computer. Cookies help us to know you better by providing operational data we can use to aid your interaction with our Web site and improve its navigation and usability.

##  Usage of personal information

EZTrader may use the information collected from you to verify your identity and contact information. We may also use this information to establish and set up your trading account, issue an account number and a secure password, maintain your account activity, and contact you with account information. This information helps us improve our services to you, customize your browsing experience and inform you about additional products, services or promotions that may be of interest to you.

Should you close your account with us, EZTrader will retain your information, but only use it to comply with regulatory requirements and to periodically contact you to offer you the opportunity to reactivate your account or participate in other valuable offers.

##  Non-affiliated third parties

EZTrader does not sell, license, lease or otherwise disclose your personal information to any third party for any reason, except as described below.

EZTrader reserves the right to disclose your personal information to third parties where required by law to regulatory, law enforcement or other government authorities. We may also disclose your information as necessary to credit reporting or collection agencies, or when necessary to protect our rights or property.

To help us improve our services to you, we may engage another business to help us to carry out certain internal functions such as account processing, fulfillment, client service, client satisfaction surveys or other data collection activities relevant to our business. We may also provide a party with client information from our database to help us to analyze and identify client needs and notify clients of product and service offerings. Use of the information shared is strictly limited to the performance of the task we request and for no other purpose. All third parties with which we share personal information are required to protect personal information in a manner similar to the way we protect personal information. Examples of information shared are identifying information such as name, mailing address, e-mail address, telephone number and information on account activity.

If at any time you choose to purchase a product or service offered by another company, for example by clicking on an advertisement on our Web site, any personal information you share with that company will no longer be controlled under our Privacy Statement. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of sites we link to and we have no control of the use or protection of information provided by you or collected by those sites. Whenever you elect to link to a co-branded Web site or to a linked Web site, you may be asked to provide registration or other information. Please note that the information you are providing is going to a third party, and you should familiarize yourself with the privacy policy published by that third party.

##  Opting out of disclosures of non-public personal information

You may direct us not to disclose non-public personal information to certain third parties. To opt out of sharing non-public personal information with third parties, please contact us as stated in the contact information listed below. Note that for joint accounts, an opt out election made by one account owner of a Joint account is applicable to all account owners of the Joint account. An opt-out election must be made for each separate account you hold at EZTrader.

If we propose to share information in a manner not covered in this Privacy Statement, we will notify you of this change by posting an addendum on the EZTrader Web site, and if appropriate, provide you an opportunity to opt out of such use.

##  The security of your personal information

We employ security software, systems, and procedures to offer you a safe and secure trading environment and protect your personal, financial and trading information.

When you open an account with us, you are issued a unique account number, User ID and a password. Only a limited number of EZTrader employees who have a need to know this information will have access to your account number, UserID, and password. Remember: you are ultimately responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your account number, UserID, and password. We strongly recommend that you do not disclose this information to any one else.

On our Web site and on our online account application, we use technology to encrypt information transmitted by or to you through our Web site.

##  Changes to this Privacy Statement

In the event EZTrader materially changes this Privacy Statement, the revised Privacy Statement will promptly be posted to the Web site and we will post a notice on our Web site informing you of such changes. You agree to accept posting of a revised Privacy Statement electronically on the Web site as actual notice to you. Any dispute over our Privacy Statement is subject to this notice and the EZTrader Customer Agreement. If you have any questions that this statement does not address, please contact a client services representative.
